Zack, Arnold Additional Aarbitration Files 5913
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Arnold Zack Additional Aarbitration Files
1989-1991
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Zack, Arnold M.
5913
8 cubic feet
8 linear ft.
Records.
5734515
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 10, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 10, 2016
Biographical / Historical
Lawyer, arbitrator, and government official; LLB Yale, 1956, MBA Harvard, 1961, MA Harvard, 1963.
Arnold Marshall Zack is an arbitrator and mediator. Beginning his labor career as a part-time election examiner for the National Labor Relations Board and as a case analyst for the U.S. Wage Stabilization Board (1950-1953), he was also a lecturer in labor economics at Simmons College, Northeastern University (1957-1963); an assistant to Saul Wallen, arbitrator, (1956-1960); director of the Labor-Management Institute of the American Academy of Arbitrators (1966-1968); and has served in various labor-related international posts for the United States government.
Other governmental service includes membership on panels for the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, the Massachusetts Public Employment Relations Board, the New York State Public Employment Relations Board, The New Jersey Public Employment Relations Board, The New York City Office of Collective Bargaining, and The National Mediation Board. Zack is also a panel member of the American Arbitration Association, and has served as the permanent arbitrator for a number of major corporations and unions and for the State of New York and the U.S. Postal Service.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Zack, Arnold.
5734515
- Purity Supreme/IBT Woburn TBD FMCS 90-05231 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- RITX Carlton/HEREIU March 26, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- WM Rosenstein & Sons/Teamsters 229 Scranton, PA (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Rutland City Board of school Directors Rutland Ed Assn, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Scope and Contents
  Oct 3
- St. Vrain/Teachers, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Dec 16
- Sanford/Sanford Police Town Hall June 25, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Scituate/Teachers AAA Boston Jan 9, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Sheahan Printing corp/GCIU Providence biltmore Oct 2, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Springfield Terminal (NMB) (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Standard Thomson/IUE Local 274 Sept 18 Bestwestern TLC. Waltham, MA, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Stop & Shop/UFCW April 24, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- TLT Construction/Carpenters AAA Boston (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Trial court/SEIU April 30, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- TWA/IAM, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- TWA/IAM June 6 JFK Plaza Hotel 9 AM, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- VA/Nage Sept 25 Brockton, MA, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Vermont Yankee/IBEW Local 300 Dec 5 Brattle, VT, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Sinai Hospital/NUHHCE Baltimore, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Oct 19
- Washington Teacher's Union/Ricks Nov 27, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Western Union/CWA Nov 20, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- WGBH/NABET Jan 3, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Wakefield School Board/NEA-NH Nov 28, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Yale Electrical Reliance in Mass Mediation Service/Suffolk June 28, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Yale Federation of Union Employees March 7, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Yale/Local 35 Sept 24, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Yale/Local 35 FUE Jan 29, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Yale/Local May 22, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Yale University/FUE local 35 July 12 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Adams County Teachers Colorado Nov 28-29 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Town of Ashland/IAFF Ashland Town Hall June 7, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Barry/Cooley Suffolk Superior Court Feb 1, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Bay State Bus/ATU Feb 2, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Bent & Bros./IUE Sept 21, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Berlin Police Commission/AFSCME (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Beth Israel Medical CTR/RWDSU March 6, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Boston Edison/UWUA Sheraton Tara Braintree, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  July 18
- Braintree/Braintree Police Club July 11, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Boston School committee/BTU June 26 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Brinderson Corp/Ironworkers Local 7 Dec 18, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Bryant College/ Bryant faculty federation Smithfield, RI March 23 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Cambridge/Police Sept 25 4 pm Cambridge Police Station, Cent Sq., 1989 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Casey & Hayes Movers, Inc/Teamsters AAA Boston Sept 25, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Champion Paper/UPIU Bangor, ME March 15, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Charlesgate Nursing Home/Dist 1199 RI Providence, RI Oct 31, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Coca Cola/RWDSU Needham Sheraton FMCS March 5, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Colorado Springs/Teachers Nov 28, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Contoocook Valley School Board/Teachers Assn. (Box 2, Folder 19)
- DuPont Chemical Workers Assn Nov 14, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- DuPont/Chemical Workers New Castle, Del Jan 9, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- DuPont De Nemours Chemical Workers New Castle, DE May 14, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- USPS/APWU July 19, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- USPS/NRLC July 24, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- USPS/NAMH July 31 Springfield, MA, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- USPS/NAMH Aug 1 NYC 1250 Broadway (Box 3, Folder 4)
- USPS/NAMH Aug 2 AMF JFK Bldg. 250, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- USPS/NAMH Aug 21 Hicksville, NY, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- USPS/NAMH Aug 23 Whippany, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- USPS/NAMH Buffalo Sept 5, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- USPS/NAMH Hackensack Sept 10, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- USPS/NAMH Sept 11, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- USPS/NAMH NYC Broadway Sept 12, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- USPS/NAMH Sept 13 Newark, NJ, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- USPS/NAMH Eatontown, NJ Sept 14, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- USPs/NAMH Buffalo, NY Oct 10, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- USPS/Postmaster Oct 1, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- USPS/NAMH North Jersey Oct 11, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- USPS/APWU Providence, RI Oct 22, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- USPs/NALC GMF Boston Oct 23, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- USPS/APWU Oct 24 Woburn, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- USPS/APWU Oct 25 NYC 341 9th Ave, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- USPS/NAMH Nov 13 Boston GMF, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- USPS/NAMH Nov 14 Mt Vernon, NY, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- USPS/NAMH Nov 15 Bronx, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- USPS/APWU Nov 16 New York 9th Ave, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- USPS/NAMH Dec 10, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- USPS/NAMH Rochester, NY 12/11, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- USPS/NAMH Dec 12, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- USPS/NAMH Springfield, MA Dec 12, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- USPS/NAMH Jan 9, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- USPS/NAMH Jan 10, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- USPS Jan 23, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- USPS Jan 23, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- USPS/NALC Buffalo, NY Jan 14, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- USPS/APWU NY, NY Jan 23, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- USPS/NAMH Boston, MA Feb 4, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- USPS/APWU Springfield, MA Feb 5, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- USPS/APWU Gen Post Office of NY Feb 6, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- USPS/NAMH NJ Feb 11, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- USPS/APWU Hicksville, NY Feb 12, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- USPS/APWU Hicksville, NY Feb 12, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- USPS/APWU Hicksville, NY Feb 12, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- EAC Operations Inc./IUOE Dec 28 Sandwich, MA, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Granby Board of Ed/Granby Ed Assn Granby, CT June 4, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Arnold M. Zack (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Procedural PLB Nos. 4796, 4797, 4798 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Grand Trunk Western/UTU PLB Jan 19, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- IRS/NTEU Oct 9 Hartford, CT, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- IRS/NTEU Dec 13&14 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- James River/UPIU Bangor, ME Oct 26, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- James River/ UPIU Dec 20, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Lexington School committee/Nage April 9, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Greater Lowell Regional school Comm/ Greater Lowell Reg Teachers Assn. Sept. 28 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Maine/MSEA July 17 10 AM Portland Holiday Inn, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Manchester/AFSCME Derryfield CC 10 AM July 9, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- MBTA (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Suffolk Superior Courthouse. Mas Med Service 1:30 Jan 30, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Middletown/Police Jan 29, 30, 31 AAA Hartford, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Mobil Oil corp/IOW AAA Philadelphia Jan 11 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- National Labor Relations Board/NLRB Union Boston Nov 29-30 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Dept. of Navy/ FEMTC Portsmouth, NH Dec 19, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- NYC Transit/ SIBA Sept 27, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- North Providence/RILDC Biltmore in Providence Feb 7 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Civil Action no.89-1778 Suffolk Superior Courthouse March 20 1:30 PM, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- PA Power & Light/IBEW Allentown, PA Jan 10, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- PA Power & Light/IBEW Allentown, PA Nov 19 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Pepsi Cola/Teamster local 493 Oct 16 Hartford, CT, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Peter Pan Bus Lines/ ATU July 3, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Providence, IAFF Biltmore, Providence March 29 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Pueblo/IBPO May 24 City Hall Pueblo, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- USPS/APWU Oct 26, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- USPS/NARC Expedited Arb. Mt Vernon, NY Nov 8, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- USPS/NAMH Nov 6 Manchester, NH, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- USPS/NAMH Dec 12 Springfield, MA, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- USPS Arb. Invoice (Box 5, Folder 5)
- USPS/APWU Sept 8 Elizabeth, NJ, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- USPS/NAMH GPO NYC Jan 16, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- USPS/NAMH Jersey City Jan 23, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- USPS/NAMH Springfield, MA Jan 24, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- USPS/NAMH Bronx Dec 14, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- USPS/APWU Springfield, MA Jan 17, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- USPS/NAMH Trenton, NJ Jan 22, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- USPS/NAMH Bronx Feb 5, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- USPS/APWU NYC Feb 12, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- USPS/NAMH NYC Feb 13, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- USPS/NAMH Jersey City Feb 14, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- USPS/NAMH Hicksville, NY Feb 16, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- USPS/NAMH GMF Springfield March 9, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- USPS/NAMH Bronx March 13, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- USPS/NAMH Bronx March 13, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- USPS/APWU Dedham March 14, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- USPS/APWU NYC March 16, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- USPS/NAMH NYC April 3, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- USPS/NAMH Springfield, MA April 4, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- USPS/NRLC Wappinger Falls April 5, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- USPS/APWU NYC April 6, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- ISPS/APWU Woburn, MA May 10, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- USPS/APWU NYC May 11, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- USPS/NAMH Bronx, NY May 16, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- USPS/NAMH NYC May 17, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- USPS/NAMH Mt Vernon, NY May 21 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- USPS/NAMH Mt Vernon, NY May 23, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- USPS/NAMH NYC June 1, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- USPS/NAMH NYC June 5, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- USPS/APWU Manchester, NH June 11, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- USPS/NAMH Kearney June 12, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- USPS/APWU Waterbury, CT June 13, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- USPS/NAMH Hicksville, NY March 1, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- USPS/NAMH New Jersey BMC March 4, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- USPS/NAMH Flushing, NY March 5, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- USPS/APWU Gen Post of NY March 13, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- USPS/APWU Gen Post of NY March 15, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- USPS/NALC Manchester, NH April 1, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- USPS/NAMH Long Island, NY April 2, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- USPS/NAMH NJ BMC, NJ April 3, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- USPS/APWU Gen Post, NY April 4, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- USPS/APWU Gen Post Office of NY May 1, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- USPS/NAMH Bronx, NY May 13, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- USPS/NAMH NJ BMC May 14, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Arnold M. Zack Trenton, NJ Arb. Invoice May 15, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- USPS/NAMH Hicksville, NY May 16, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- USPS/NALC Boston, MA July 9, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- USPs/APWU Edison, NJ July 16, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- USPs/NALC Modified 15 Procedure Woburn, MA June 17, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Lamoille Valley RR/UTU (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Keane Police Keane City Hall, NY July 17, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Kennedy Studio/Beal June 11, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Immigration & Naturalization/AFGE Portland, ME Oct 17 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- IRS/NTEU Norwalk, CT April 23-24, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Landmark Med Center/FNHP Cranston, RI Dec 20, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- W. Warick/IBPO W. Warick, RI Dec 13, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- James River/UPIU Groveton, NH March 11, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Air Force/NAGE, Local RI-8 Dec 16, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Boise Cascade/UPIU Rumford, ME March 19, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Boise Cascade Corp/UPIU Rumford, ME Sept 19, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Brockton School/NAGE Boston, MA June 25, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Princeton, NJ Jan 25 Capitol Publishing, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Cascade Diamond/UPTIU #1847 Ho Jo's West Springfield, MA Jan 16, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Centrex/Teamsters Providence, RI Oct 4, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Cheyenne/Inter'l Assoc. of Fire Cheyenne WO April 25 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- CT College/CT Teachers CT May 3, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- CT Teachers/Staff Union of CT Berline, CT (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Consultec/Comm of Mass Ropes & Gray Boston, MA Sept 13, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Con-Val Cancellation Jan 24, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Contoocook/Con-Val Peterborough, NH march 12, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Conway School Board/ Education Support North Conway, NH May 22 AAA (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Dade County/Firefighters Assoc. Nov 26, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Derecktor/USWA Local 9057 Middletown, RI Dec 6, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Dow Jones/GCIU Boston, MA Jan 25, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Ebasco Constructors/RI Carpenters Warwick, RI Jan 30, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Essex county Gas/USWA Haverhill, MA June 10, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Fairbanks Scale/UE, local 234 St. Johnsburg May 2, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Arnold Zack Arb Bill Boston, MA (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Greater Lawrence Sanitary/Employ Association North Andover Jan 4, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Armstrong/IUE local 269 MA March 20, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Harley Davidson/Int'l Assn. of Mach York, PA Aug 20, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Litchfield School (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Lottery/SEIU Boston, MA Nov 29, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Maine, State of MSEA Augusta, ME Jan 8, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- State of Maine/MSEA Augusta, ME Oct 30, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- State of Maine/MSEA 2/12, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Manufacturers Railroad case (Box 8, Folder 6)
- NAA: Comm. On Development of Arbitrators Larry Susskind (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Milton Hosp/IBFO Milton, MA July 8, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Mobil Oil/Independent Oil Workers PA Feb 15, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Montaup Electric/UWUA Somerset, MA Sept 25, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- New Fairfield/Education Assoc. New Fairfield Commons, CT Feb 8, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- NIDR (Box 8, Folder 12)
- City of Pawtucket/RI Council 94 AFSCME HoJo's Pawtucket, RI May 21, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Rogers corp/UPIU Norwich, CT Nov 6, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Sheraton/Local 217 HERE Hartford, CT Aug 26, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Trumbull Schools/trumbull Ed. Assoc. Trumbull. CT AAA April 22, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Poultney/Poultney Teacher Sept 23 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Rockland County/Fed. Of Teachers Dec 3-4 NY (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Royal Electric/IBEW Providence, RI Jan 28, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Sands Hotel Employees Union Sept 27, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- NEHCEU, District 1199 and slater Health Center (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Tropworld Hotel Casino/Hotel Employees 10 AM Atlantic city Dec 13 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Trumbull Schools/Ed. Assoc. Trumbull, CT Dec 10, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- TWAMCI Kansas city, MI Aug 13, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Wellesley College/ Well Police Jan 11, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- West Warwick/ AFSCMEWarwick RI HOJO (Box 8, Folder 26)
- WHDH/AFIRA Boston, MA June 2 + 4 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Woman & Infant's Hosp/SEIU Providence, RI Feb 22, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Wyman-Gordon/USWA Worcester, MA Oct 23 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Yale/Local 34 July 25, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Yale/local 34 Sept 24, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Yale/Local 34 Oct 8, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Yale/Local 34 Nov 4, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Yale/Local 34 Dec 17, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 34)